[Previously on "ALL or NOTHING"]
[EGYPT]
The pyramid.
The Sphinx.
The capital, Cairo.
[ALL or NOTHING]
A mysterious country.
I'm really in Egypt.
[The six men arrive in the golden city]
It’s been one of my dreams.
What does this mean?
I didn't get it!
[Goofball eldest brother, LEETEUK]
Why can’t I understand this?
I didn't understand it.
[Knock knock]
Something healthy means smaller portions.
[Strategist SHINDONG]
This was all part of the plan.
SHINDONG, you’re super strategic.
[The gentle and soft type?!]
[A man of unexpected charms, DAWN]
I should show you my unexpected side.
Wow!
I’m all about chasing romance.
[Team Romance, JOHNNY]
In a way, it could be romantic, right?
I'm gonna win, no matter what.
[100% competitive, YOHAN]
Nice! YOHAN! Show us! Show us!
I’m in my prime these days.
[The golden youngest, JISUNG]
JISUNG, the man with two hearts!
JISUNG’s really good at this.
"ALL or NOTHING".
[What will they do in this place?]
[Depending on the mission results]
[The princes indulge in luxury]
Whoa, this place is so luxurious!
This is so great.
Wow, I’m getting goosebumps.
[And the paupers lose it all...]
I don’t wanna be a pauper.
What am I supposed
to do if I end up a pauper?
I don’t think I can be a pauper…
["ALL or NOTHING" First Mission: The Pharaoh’s Table]
Will we become a prince or a pauper?
[After eating everything and clearing the plates]
We just have to eat well and finish the chosen courses.
[at the restaurants reserved in order]
Yes, it’s delicious.
It's good!
- It's good?
- Yeah!
[The first team to reach the meetup spot wins!]
The first team that gets
to the meetup spot wins.
[A total of 7 reserved locations]
We don’t know which is
dessert, meat, or seafood here.
[Depending on their decisions]
I was hoping the restaurants were all close by.
[Today’s fate]
I hope they're nearby.
[will be decided]
I want to go somewhere close.
[I'll decide my own fate]
No!
- Nice!
- Good job!
[There's no way I'm being a pauper…!]
Good job! YOHAN! Nice!
Alright, here we go!
[And the battle officially begins!]
Let’s go!
[Food first, battle later]
Wow, this is amazing.
It smells delicious.
[A feast of food unfolds before them]
Wow! The view is amazing!!
This is seriously good!
[Digging in without hesitation]
It tastes amazing.
This is really tasty.
[With the younger members stepping up]
JISUNG, you really eat fast.
You're really eating well today.
[The first course gets cleared in no time]
Wow!
[The long-awaited moment
of choosing the second restaurant]
[Team LEETEUK ends up at a nearby restaurant]
It's somewhere close, LEETEUK.
- Hey, it's right nearby! Let's go!
- We're good, we're good! Let's go!
Yeah.
[Team SHINDONG gets stuck at a restaurant far away]
Oh, it's the farthest!
[What will be their fate…?]
[CHAPTER.2]
[The one who sows the wind, reaps the storm]
[Team LEETEUK peacefully enjoys the meal]
I think it has curry powder and turmeric.
- Oh!
- It does, right?
[A dark figure
slowly creeps up on them]
Who…are you?
Who are you?
Oh, you scared me…!
[Just earlier]
Seeing that we haven't taken the overpass…
[Team SHINDONG, who chose the other restaurant]
There are more foreign cars now.
But I hope
the other team gets big portions.
[Picked a place way too far away]
[Along with Cairo’s brutal rush hour]
This is when the traffic is heavy.
I see.
Oh, we lost this.
What should we do?
[Team LEETEUK is almost done eating]
[But they still haven't arrived yet]
Ugh, this is bad.
[The gap keeps widening]
Should we hurry and use an item?
[Will they just lose like this?]
I got so nervous that we might lose.
Oh, okay.
[Let’s use an attack item]
Let's use it!
- It's already hard deboning fish on your own.
- Yeah, you're right.
YOHAN, can you read it out loud?
What does it say?
"One hand's just for support"!
Nice!
[Used the attack item]
Ta-da!
"One hand's just for support"!
We will use it now.
[Hehe]
Try deboning the fish with this!
Oh, it's done, it's done.
- They have the same strategy as us!
- And on top of that…
[JISUNG & JOHNNY get tied up]
LEETEUK, you don't have to tie your hands, right?
Since we're on this side?
Isn't it just
the two of us getting tied together?
(Please lower your hand)
Am I getting tied too?
[Aha...!]
[Chosen to get both hands tied]
Oh, I somehow ended up in the middle.
- Should we do it like this, or that?
- I ended up being in the middle.
[JISUNG’s hands get tightly tied]
Isn’t this something we should decide?
Did you talk about
how to tie us together?
[I’m supposed to be leading this game...!]
I need to take charge of this game, so…
I'll go over there.
And if you're...
If you’re full, I’ll just eat it all.
And if you're full…
[JISUNG, your hands are tied]
I’ll just eat it all.
JISUNG.
[JISUNG, where’s your fork?]
Sit down, you sit.
Sit down.
[You take the lead]
Our JISUNG, open wide!
[Somehow feeling like he misspoke]
Whoa.
Wow.
Our JISUNG, open wide!
Slowly, slowly!
LEETEUK, you're doing this
because you can't eat anymore, huh?
[Bullseye]
No! I can still eat. I can.
No, no! Just wait.
I'm gonna eat.
But please don't push yourself.
No, I can eat, just watch.
JOHNNY is so cold.
[I am?]
He's cold.
Why’s that?
[This guy]
He knows me way too well.
[Unnecessarily romantic]
But LEETEUK, don't you think it's so romantic right now?
[The beautifully flowing Nile River]
The Nile River right here...!
[And our sweet LEETEUK...]
Our JISUNG, open wide!
JISUNG, open wide!
Slowly, slowly!
I really love fish
that's been grilled
with my favorite spices.
So when that dish came out,
I enjoyed it a lot.
[Q. Did you get closer to LEETEUK?]
Did being tied up bring you two closer?
I think it just
made us drift further apart.
For the first time,
LEETEUK felt hard to…
He felt harder…to approach, yes…
Oh, but hey…
[The hard-to-approach
big bro has back pain]
Oh, my back.
[Thud]
[The type
that requires a lot of care]
I didn't get wet. I'm good.
LEETEUK, you could
just come over here.
Oh, you're right.
JOHNNY.
As expected, JOHNNYUS.
[With the high-maintenance big bro
and JOHNNYUS & JISUNG stepping up]
It’s seriously tough
when your hands are tied.
[They ate without breaking a sweat]
Our JISUNG, open wide!
Since there are no chopsticks here,
I hope they debone
everything with their hands.
Oh, that's nice.
[They used a fork like a pro]
Oh, I was gonna debone it.
I really want LEETEUK
to sit right in the middle.
[Crushing even their tiniest hope]
Oh, JOHNNY! As expected!
So neatly!
We got lucky,
because we finished most of it,
and there were no bones.
It felt like
they were helping us win!
[Damage: 0]
We weren't affected at all.
[After flawlessly blocking]
Will you show us your plate?
[Team SHINDONG's attack]
I checked everything thoroughly.
[Team LEETEUK clears the seafood course]
We're done!
All done, finished!
- We really finished this one.
- Done!
[Just then,
SHINDONG makes a spy call]
(We got a call!)
Can they not answer it?
Because their hands are tied up?
[They’re still blissfully unaware]
Maybe they can’t pick up because their hands are tied.
LEETEUK!
Nice to hear from you!
I know your hands
are tied right now.
My hands?
Yes.
We're tied up, you punk.
[So happy]
[Doing his best to appear
as hopeless as possible]
But wait,
are you still on the move?
[Correct]
We’re still on the move.
[WANGGEOZ are
happy on both sides]
It's so far…
[Wrapping up the call]
Okay!
Continue to enjoy your meal.
Yes, we will.
Thanks for the handcuffs.
Thank you.
They think we haven’t eaten yet
We can take these off now, right?
But there was nothing
on their plates when I looked.
- The food didn't come out yet.
- I guess they haven't opened up the food yet.
Oh, this is easy!
I'm gonna easily become a prince!
While doing this program,
I thought that
I'd take it easy and relax.
[Grinning]
[Team SHINDONG finally arrives
after the tour through Cairo]
Huh?
The smell is like…!
SHINDONG.
The pot is huge.
Wait, what is this?
[It's this far away, and the portions are huge?]
Oh wow, the smell is like…!
[The bread (eish) appears again]
As expected, this is here too.
- Oh!
- I guess you always wrap it with this here.
There are gloves for your hands.
Huh?
Oh, you're right.
I guess we're eating with our hands.
[What could possibly be inside?]
What is it?
Wow, it's pretty big.
- Let’s open it right away.
- Okay.
- First, it's warm. It's warm.
- Let's do it.
- Oh, it's warm?
- Yes.
[What dish is expensive in Korea, too?]
One, two, three!
Okay, one two three!
Huh?
Oh.
- Ahahaha!
- Oh!
[Frozen]
No, but wait…
There's so much!
[A huge pile of shrimp appears]
So much…!
(Expensive)
There's so much!
[Did Team LEETEUK use an attack item?]
Did they add a serving?
[Nope]
They didn't for this?
This is jumbo...
grilled jumbo shrimp...
I’ve never seen
so many shrimp at once.
Even in Korea,
I don't eat that many.
And Korea's known
for being generous with food.
We don't eat shrimp like that.
The grilled jumbo shrimp…
It's not even jumbo shrimp season.
[Speechless]
This is jumbo shrimp…
[An expensive dish even in Korea]
[Egypt, embracing
the Mediterranean and Red Seas]
[Freshly caught shrimp
straight from two seas]
[All you need is
shrimp, spices, and fire]
[Grilled king prawns]
(Looks like a lot,
but will shrink once peeled)
[Forget it, just eat]
Hey, eat! Hurry! What are we waiting for! Just eat!
Hey, just eat!
I think we need to hurry and eat.
[What will be Team SHINDONG's fate?]
Hey, just eat.
Nice.
"The Pharaoh's Table",
the full-course dining experience.
[Third course]
We only have the meat course left.
[Time to choose the meat keyword]
Meat, nice!
Before I reveal the keywords,
[Sharing the current location before the keyword reveal]
let me share our current location.
But even if I look,
I don't really know.
[Team LEETEUK's current location]
So, we just ate right here.
[Team SHINDONG's current location]
[Only three spots remain now]
This is actually the best spot.
[A 10-minute distance]
Right.
This could be the place.
[A 10-minute distance]
As long as it's not this one.
[A 45-minute distance]
[One of the three is]
As long as it's not this one.
[a whopping 45-minute trip]
Honestly, this is the best spot.
Aw, man.
JOHNNY, I’m trusting your choice.
[Lucky JOHNNY]
Because of all your choices today,
[who guided Team LEETEUK all day]
things turned out so great.
[He led the team with a romance-chasing strategy]
Actually, pizza's fast.
Let's just choose romance.
- I'm only trusting JOHNNY.
- It’s right next to here.
[Today, I'm only trusting JOHNNY…!]
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
[I trust you, JOHNNY]
I'll follow you.
Okay, okay.
Let’s go.
[Revealing the long-awaited keyword for meat]
Here's the keyword for meat.
The keyword for meat is simple.
Beef or lamb?
[A. Boiled meat / B. Grilled meat]
Boiled meat versus grilled meat.
Oh, the boiled meat…
The thing from earlier! That's right.
[Which will be the better choice?]
Doesn't boiled meat sound kind of tough?
But…
How did we make it this far?
We've been chasing after romance.
- That’s right.
- Exactly.
- We chased after romance!
- Romance Boy! RomBo!
But
we came to Egypt.
Do you want
boiled meat or grilled meat?
[Alright, let’s be honest]
Let’s just be real.
- No?
- Be honest, be honest.
Grilled, grilled, grilled.
[Grilled tastes better, right...?]
Grilled meat is really delicious.
Grilled meat is definitely tastier.
Oh, the reason is…
Do you think they ate
boiled meat back in the day?
[They probably ate grilled meat]
They ate grilled meat.
Yeah, they ate grilled meat, for sure.
If we came to Egypt,
we should eat like the Egyptians!
[Perfectly romantic logic]
As expected, JOHNNYUS!
[Final pick: B. Grilled meat]
Then it’s gotta be grilled.
Hey, the music just started playing!
Is it "A" or "B"?
[Will JOHNNY’s call be right again?]
[10 minutes away]
[45 minutes away]
[A 33.3% chance of failure]
[What will be Team LEETEUK's fate?]
As long as it's not this one.
Oh, man.
Wow, but that place…
As long as it's not that one!
[Revealing the keyword choice]
You picked grilled meat.
After choosing,
I'll share the location with you.
Oh...
[B. Grilled Meat]
[The 45-minute journey is chosen]
[Stuck with the 33.3% chance of failure]
Oh, let's go.
Let’s head out now.
We really have to go quickly.
Wow.
The moment
the third distance was revealed,
I thought we were gonna lose.
Honestly, the grilled meat
was what I really wanted to eat.
[This must be a trap]
It's like the staff
[set up by the staff]
would assume we'd pick the grilled meat,
[Then, boiled meat is the way to go]
so I was thinking we should pick
the boiled meat instead.
But JOHNNY was
all about chasing romance
and spewing nonsense,
and so,
things started going downhill…
LEETEUK kept saying
he would just follow me.
And honestly,
I just left it up to fate.
[Just chasing after romance]
Yeah.
[Let's calm down and get going]
Let’s go, but they’re still on their second course.
Let's go!
(Eating)
[B. Grilled meat]
I had a feeling
the boiled meat was gonna be closer.
[Today’s discovery]
Hey, if you peel it, it gets smaller.
[Shrimp gets smaller
when you peel the skin]
Hey, just eat it.
It really is tasty.
Oh, but it really looks yummy.
Mmm.
[DAWN, in charge of seafood, takes a bite]
I eat a lot of seafood.
Wow!
[YOHAN takes a big bite too]
Mmm!
Wow, it really tastes good.
The food here
really suits our taste buds.
[Satisfied]
It really does.
I know, right?
If we don't speed up here,
[Team LEETEUK: CLEAR, CLEAR, Meat, Dessert]
you know we'll be in trouble, right?
[We must catch up]
Wow, but we're in trouble.
[Team SHINDONG:
CLEAR, Seafood, Meat, Dessert]
[For the record,
if we can introduce this guy on the left…]
DAWN, you can do this!
[Egypt’s]
[Newly Rising Food Fighter]
[DAWN]
[DAWN (The biggest light eater in Korea)]
People have many prejudices about me.
"He's probably not going to eat."
[Source: DAWN’s social media]
People think I’m vegan.
[Actually an omnivore]
Because people assume I'm vegan,
[Eating even a little would be more than enough]
if I eat, it'll definitely exceed expectations.
When you rewatch the footage,
[Shrimp slayer]
I actually ate 15 of them.
This is pretty good
[DAWN went beyond expectations]
It'll definitely exceed expectations.
It really is tasty though.
[And the guy in the middle]
[YOHAN, eating like it’s his first meal]
Rather, if it tasted bad,
we’d be like,
"Why is this so bad?"
- But it actually tastes good.
- Yeah, it's tasty.
[First course]
The problem is, I’m actually starting to feel a little full.
I'm starving.
[Still hungry after the first meal]
I want to hurry and go eat!
We can't rest right now.
We have to go right away.
[Q. Are you a big eater?]
Do you usually eat a lot?
Yeah.
[KIM YOHAN (Big eater)]
As long as it's not bad, I can eat a lot.
[Seriously eating a lot]
If we didn't eat the one before this
and started with this,
we would've finished faster.
[Lastly, the guy on the right]
It’s tasty,
but this little thing is upsetting.
(Picks up the bread)
[Burning with determination]
We have to eat, no choice.
[The leader rallies the team]
We gotta push through.
Honestly, all the food
we picked was really good
[We ate as fast as possible]
We ate as quickly as we possibly could.
Before the other team uses an item…
[God-tier leader, SHINDONG]
It would be bad if another serving was added.
[While Team SHINDONG]
Surely after we finish this,
[was clearing the plates]
they won't add another serving, right?
[B. Grilled meat]
Let’s go!
[Team LEETEUK sets off on their long journey]
Alright, let’s roll!
We're in trouble.
There's traffic.
[There's…traffic?]
Why is there traffic here?
Is it just here?
[There is…traffic!]
[45 minutes away]
[Still a long road ahead...]
Hey, hurry and eat!
[While Team LEETEUK is running late]
Let's quickly eat and go.
[Team SHINDONG has to close the gap]
Okay, we're done, right?
Did you finish everything?
[Only shrimp shells left]
Yes.
[At this pace, there is hope]
Did you finish everything?
We finished everything.
There's hope for this!
I thought, "It could be okay,"
so we ate quickly.
(Production team)
[Inspection Time]
We ate it all.
These are what we peeled earlier.
We really ate everything.
You hid the bread.
[The bread peeks from under the shrimp shells]
You hid the bread here.
Ugh, why would you find this?
[It was too obvious to just ignore]
Oh, come on.
You hid the bread.
There's bread hidden here too.
[SHINDONG's Bakery]
She found that!
Come on!
My plate's really clean.
(Can you help?)
Just eat a little bit for me.
But seriously, the bread…
[Super pressed for time]
You kinda get really sick of it.
[Should've just eaten it
with the shrimp earlier]
[Chew, chew chew]
[Bread cleared]
Oh.
[Only shrimp shells left on the plate]
No, like, we really eat a lot.
[Team SHINDONG: Seafood course, CLEARED]
We finished it all.
Alright, next!
[Gotta pick somewhere nearby now]
Hey, let’s choose well this time.
Let's go
somewhere close this time.
But we don't know what's close!
[Guaranteed to be paupers if they go any farther]
We’re already too far out.
Oh, you're right.
But if we go all the way to the left,
we're really in trouble.
If that happens, let's just not go there
and head to our accommodation.
[Might as well just go to the pauper's accommodation]
Just go to the pauper's accommodation.
- Just go and sleep early.
- That just might be the smarter move.
Okay, the next mission.
[Revealing the third keyword]
Alright, here's the keyword.
[Team LEETEUK picked B. Grilled meat]
One, two, three!
Grilled meat.
[B. Grilled meat]
[75 minutes away
from Team SHINDONG's location]
[Meanwhile,
the unrevealed options]
[A. Boiled meat and Dessert]
[are close together]
[Will Team SHINDONG]
After some discussion,
[pick A. Boiled meat?]
choose the restaurant with the keyword you like.
[A. Boiled meat VS B. Grilled meat]
Is it pork belly or boiled pork?
(Boiled Pork / Pork Belly)
It's kind of like that.
[This team prefers grilled meat too]
Honestly, meat should be grilled.
But you know,
if you grill it,
the portion size shrinks.
Oh, when you grill it?
[B. Grilled meat has a smaller portion?!]
When you boil it, it soaks up the water.
The moisture evaporates.
No, but, SHINDONG.…
The staff said
they prepared something delicious, right?
- That's right.
- Yeah.
- So I think grilled meat is better.
- Grilled meat is better.
[Let's go with grilled meat]
Grilled meat is better.
[B. Grilled meat]
[But if they pick B. Grilled meat]
[they'll be stuck in traffic like Team LEETEUK]
I think my knees are gonna bruise.
Oof, I feel like I'm gonna die.
[B. Grilled meat]
Because…
[Possibly deciding on the worst possible move]
they wouldn’t make us eat something inedible.
Should we go with
what our gut's saying, or what?
But the thing is…!
What we said on the way here
was to choose
the opposite the next time.
[On the way to the second course]
This is such a bummer.
- We had a chance to flip things around.
- I know, right?
How about picking
the opposite for the third course?
[Decided to go against their intuition]
So the opposite of what our guts say?
We got way too strategic
and didn't even think
about the distance.
[A. Boiled meat: 35 minutes away]
Yeah, we said that. Right.
[B. Grilled meat: 75 minutes away]
We said that.
No, but…
Let's say we picked A. Boiled meat,
and if we go even farther away…
Oh…
I don't think it'll be like that.
I think boiled meat is closer.
From what I can tell,
boiled meat is closer.
For the second round,
we went with what our guts told us,
and we ended up farther away.
We gotta use our brains for this.
[Go with what doesn't draw us in]
Let’s pick what doesn't draw us in for the third one.
[Let’s do the opposite of what we want]
This time, let’s go against what we want
and see how that plays out.
[A. Boiled meat: 35 minutes away]
Should we go with boiled meat?
[B. Grilled meat: 75 minutes away]
Let’s go with the boiled meat!
Guys, let's go with boiled meat!
One, two, three!
[Picked A. Boiled meat]
"A"!
[B. Grilled Meat]
[A. Boiled Meat]
[Team SHINDONG's
odds of winning shoot up!]
- That's right.
- Oh, thank goodness, thank goodness for real!
Huh??
- We're here.
- They went!
- They went there! They went there!
- They went, they went!
[Confirmed that Team LEETEUK
is heading toward B. Grilled meat]
[A. Boiled Meat / B. Grilled Meat]
[Both teams are neck and neck again]
- They went for grilled meat?
- They went to the grilled meat place?
[The game is back to square one!]
The grilled meat place is this "X" here, right?
[Will Team SHINDONG]
[make a comeback?]
Let’s go, let’s go!
- Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
- Let's go! Let's go!
We can win this!
We got it.
We got this one.
Oh, our luck…!
I think I vibe well with Egypt.
[Team LEETEUK: CLEAR, CLEAR, Meat, Dessert]
If we had picked grilled meat,
[Team SHINDONG: CLEAR, CLEAR, Meat, Dessert]
it would’ve been a disaster
[Looking back, it was a brilliant move]
Switching at the end was a stroke of genius.
For now, I think we did well
[Still worried about the next restaurant]
picking somewhere close…
We still have
the extra serving item coming.
[Plus, there are
attack items still left]
We'll get the extra serving,
play the coin-flipping game…
[Just then, a spy call comes in]
They're calling, they're calling.
They're calling.
LEETEUK is calling.
We're still in the car, LEETEUK!
[Starting with a lie]
Are you on the move after eating, or what?
We’re still on the move.
Why is the traffic so bad here?
Lies!
It's so far.
[Lying again]
It’s too far!
Lies!
- No, seriously!
- For real.
Why are you being like that?
(Looking full)
Seeing DAWN's face,
you already ate
and are going…Where are you going?
[Another lie]
B. Grilled meat.
[Third course]
But it's so far from here.
[Team LEETEUK: B. Grilled meat]
Oh, from end to end?
[Team SHINDONG: A. Boiled meat]
Yeah, it's from one end to the other.
[Lying like it's his second nature]
LEETEUK, where are you? Where are you at?
What did we pick again?
[Lying till the end]
A. Boiled meat.
We picked boiled meat.
[The call is full of lies from both teams]
Oh, boiled meat is so close, though.
It’s literally right next door.
Man, I’m so jealous.
We have to go
from end to end, so it's far for us.
We're like gentle sheep,
so we'll believe
everything you say.
- Why would we lie?
- No, but it's real.
…Lies.
[No trust whatsoever]
- We're serious.
- Seriously?
Then, LEETEUK,
[Feeling them out]
are we meeting at B. Grilled meat?
We picked A. Boiled meat!
[A tense battle of lies]
Come on, don’t lie! You said grilled meat.
[Back]
Did we pick B. Grilled meat?
[And forth]
No, A. Boiled meat.
[The pointless mind game ends]
Anyway, we'll see you
at the final meetup place.
[Meanwhile, Team LEETEUK falls into confusion with no info]
I think they're telling the truth.
- Because…
- Yeah.
I think they're on the same road.
[While LEETEUK and JOHNNY totally fall for it]
Right? They're going from one end to the other.
They definitely picked grilled meat.
[The correct answer]
Team SHINDONG checked the map after us,
so they probably know
we're headed towards B. Grilled meat.
[Young JISUNG's the only one in his right mind]
They were holding in their laughter…
I could tell
they were trying not to laugh.
[Therefore, Team SHINDONG is A. Boiled meat…]
I’m 100% sure they picked boiled meat.
I looked in the background.
- It's similar to ours.
- Yeah, the scenery is the same as ours.
[Team SHINDONG's road backdrop is similar to ours!]
It's the highway on the opposite side.
Oh, and there were
no cars next to them.
[Roads usually look alike…]
No, from what I can tell, they wouldn't pick boiled meat.
I think it's real.
- I think they really got grilled meat.
- Because…
But there’s gotta be
at least one restaurant we overlap on.
[Probability factor enters the chat]
Statistically, there’s no way we don’t cross paths once.
I like data-based stuff.
A matter of probability.
We'll run into each other
at least once during this course.
Statistically speaking.
It’s only a 50% chance.
No!
We’re the first…
JOHNNY...
Just think about it.
[And so, the probability debate begins]
It’s gotta be one or the other.
The fish place didn’t overlap.
So yeah,
the probability is only 50%.
Yeah,
and there are 3 courses. Look.
[Avoiding]
But you can't split the three like that.
Out of the three…Look.
[Arrived at the third course, while avoiding probability]
We still made it. Nice.
[Team LEETEUK: CLEAR, CLEAR, Meat, Dessert]
Kebab.
Oh, it's lamb.
[Heading straight
into the restaurant]
Come on in.
[Come on!]
[Seen right from the entrance]
[An interior with modern vibes]
[And a grand display of luxurious items]
[What kind of dish
awaits in this palace-like place?]
Wow… What is this…?
- Hey, what? Wow! This place…!
- Wow.
[A bit overwhelmed by the restaurant’s vibe]
Wow.
Achoo!
- LEETEUK, don't kill the vibe.
- Oh, sorry.
This place makes me
feel like…a king!
[Passed the vibe check]
Wow!
[And welcoming them is]
Are we eating right away?
[The scary silver lid...]
I think it's gonna be
a lot of food…
One…
[What’s the grilled meat in the meat course...?]
One, two, three!
- Lamb.
[Lamb]
[Ground lamb mixed with spices and seasoning]
[A charcoal fire massage
infused with a smoky aroma]
[From local-style meatballs called kofta]
[to juicy lamb chops
that explode with flavor]
[Kofta & Grilled Lamb Chops]
[A huge portion]
Thank you for this food.
[WOW]
Wow!
- This…
- How many are there?
- Oh, but…this is more than I thought.
- It's a lot.
I momentarily forgot
[Egyptian hospitality is always so generous...]
that we have to eat everything.
[Pre-ordering digestive aid]
Can we get colas early, please?
But this is the last one!
[Let’s enjoy it deliciously till the end]
Let’s enjoy it together.
Oh, thank you.
[Anyway, enjoy a sophisticated culinary experience]
I should use the sauce for flavor.
[featuring some
high-end meat cutting]
I heard this place is super famous.
It’s delicious.
- It's good.
You don’t even
need to dip it in the sauce.
[Following after LEETEUK,
JOHNNY takes a bite]
Is it already seasoned?
- Yeah, it's lightly marinated.
- Right?
There’s something
brushed on the outside.
[Charcoal-grilled to golden perfection]
And it barely smells like lamb.
You can barely smell it.
I sniffed at it first.
[Smoky and fresh
lamb chops with no gamey smell]
- This is good.
- So good.
[JISUNG also takes a big bite]
You don’t even need to dip it in the sauce.
- Is it already seasoned?
- Yeah, it's lightly marinated.
- Right?
- Yeah.
There’s something
brushed on the outside.
[Happiness 0.00 / Proud 0.00]
And it barely smells like lamb.
[Impressed 0.00 / Satisfied 0.01]
You can barely smell it.
[Flustered 99.99]
I smelled it first.
Is it not good?
No, I…It's okay.
Just okay?!
It…It's okay…?
It's your…It's your
first time eating lamb, huh?!
I think it's
my first time trying lamb chops…
Oh! So this is
what lamb smells like…!
I'm smelling it
for the first time in my life…
This lamb smell.
Oh really?
[First time smelling lamb in Egypt]
But this is actually not that strong.
Oh really?
It barely has a smell.
I added another dish I can't eat.
It's called lamb…
Ssp…It got added.
[No…]
[Just face it, JISUNG…]
[No, it's okay!]
[Your big bros got you]
I'll work hard on this.
I’m going in for round two.
I'll try dipping it in sauce too.
The sauce is good.
You don’t need to dip it too much.
Wow.
- Good, right?
- Yeah.
Right?
[It's all about the sauce]
Slap on the sauce.
- I'm gonna dip it in sauce, no matter what.
- Slap on the sauce.
[Sauce prescribed
for the lamb newbie]
Hey, it's so much better.
Oh?! Oh... you’re right.
[Following the eldest’s lead]
Alright, let's just eat without thinking about it.
Don't keep thinking about it.
[Team LEETEUK
diligently moves forward]
This is delicious!
[Team SHINDONG arrives for their third course]
Ready to roll?
[CLEAR, CLEAR, Meat, Dessert]
Whoa!
Wow, this restaurant…
Oh, there's something…
different about it
from the other places.
[After pushing through
the bustling crowd]
[Team SHINDONG arrives at the third restaurant]
Oh?
[They arrived
way later than Team LEETEUK]
[But the portion looks small]
The portion size looks small.
- I know, right?
- Right?
[Filled with the aroma of a famous restaurant]
And it smells so good.
There are so many people here.
They said
it's a really famous place.
[The boiled meat for the meat course is…?]
Alright, here we go!
One, two, three!
- Huh?
What is this...?
[Chewy ox trotters]
[and ox knee cartilage
packed with rich collagen]
[slow-cooked with aromatic spices]
[A traditional
Egyptian health booster]
[Kaware']
[Small portion]
What is this...?
[The dish feels somewhat like Korean food]
Doesn't it have a Korean vibe to it?
This food…
Is this the correct food?
Oh?! This seems delicious!
Oh, wait, wait.
What’s this?
[Suddenly, a tray appears]
What's this?
- What's this?
- There's more?
What's this?
- What's this?
- Open it up.
[It's me, the attack item]
The gentleman over there sent it.
[So, it's finally arrived]
Ugh! Seriously!
[A moment ago]
Should we do what we need to do?
We'll use our item!
"The gentleman over here sent it".
…I think it's…"over there"…
- Is it "over there"?
- Yeah.
[Anyway, attack item activated!]
Nice!
Enjoy your meal!
[You mean "finally"]
They "gladly" used it!
Aw, man.
[Start with the additional serving]
Please enjoy the first one they sent.
Oh, the first one they sent…
- I'll taste it first.
- Yeah, taste it first.
[Light eater → Big eater]
[DAWN, who's changing up his image, goes first]
But it's kind of
like ox bone soup.
[Korean ox bone soup + a hint of curry...?]
It’s like ox bone soup with a hint of curry.
If you look here,
it’s kind of
like ox knee soup!
- Oh, not bad.
- Right?
Yeah, I think it's gonna be good.
[KIM YOHAN]
[On an intermittent fast (1 hour completed)]
Oh, the smell!
Yeah, it smells
very savory and rich.
[Say something, please]
Is it okay?
It's really good!
- Really?
- Yeah.
Then, we can eat this, right?
[After finishing the attack item, the game resumes]
You have to finish one bowl first.
Oh, really?
Hey, you need to eat faster, then.
Yeah, it can't be helped.
- What?
- Hey, you have to eat quickly!
- Try some…!
- No, you dipped your spoon in it,
- so you eat it first.
- But you really need to try a spoonful.
- Oh, really?
- Yes, really.
[To match the wait]
[A big spoonful]
Hmm?
It's good, right?
It doesn't have a smell at all!
It doesn't have
that gamey meat smell.
This is so good!
[A rich broth simmered for hours]
Oh, now I get why this place is famous
[with a chewy, savory texture that melts in your mouth]
Koreans will definitely love this.
- It'd go well with alcohol.
- But it's slightly mild.
I think it's a bit
mild for us to eat.
Mmm! Mhm!
Oh?! Hmm?!
[Wait, what?!]
It's delicious!
[And then...]
Are you full?
[Gulping it down as the leader]
It's really delicious.
[Cleared the extra serving attack item!]
[Victory vibes are kicking in!]
But honestly, this much food is…
Hey, if we eat fast,
I think we can
turn the tables at this rate!
[The game starts now!]
Hey, we can totally turn this around.
This is…Hey.
[Let’s really hit the gas!]
Oh, this will be gone in no time, but…
Ugh…
[Attack item activated]
They used a mission.
Oh, come on!
They're using them all here...
Ugh!
[Even used their last attack card]
That traditional coin game!
[The traditional coin game]
We'll send one more your way!
Let's hit them hard
with one big blow!
[Fed up]
No, like…
It's just evil.
It's so mean…
[RULE]
[Flip all 6 coins at once]
Let's be quick with it.
Just try it out.
[Carefully]
Oh, my hands are so...
[Getting into position]
small.
Hey, how long
is this gonna take…
Just hit it a few times!
You can just
quickly do it a few times...
[No flip]
Oh, this is bad…
Oh, this is really bad.
What are we gonna do about this?
Can we even get the hang of it?
[Super stuck]
Hey, this is seriously bad.
[Will they make it out by today…?]
Hey hey, wait a sec. So this… So…
[And the issue here is]
[They're slowing down
because they're stuffed]
No, I'll eat that, I'm fine.
Oh!
You should still give it a try.
You want me to eat this?
No, I'm gonna eat
another one of those.
Oh, but still!
[Brotherly love blooms through the fullness]
No, no.
LEETEUK!
- Good food is… Oh!
- Don't lose your sense of romance!
Oof! Romance!
Romance Bro, you first.
[Little bro, you first]
No, seriously, I’m good.
[Big bro, you first]
You should try it once.
Wait, I'm eating!
It's right here!
Right here, see?
Open wide!
No.
Can you cut it smaller?
Please slice it for me.
It's too big.
[A true class act
can smile through the fullness]
It's been 3 hours and 42 minutes
since we started eating.
No, like…
We were told
to enjoy a trip in Egypt,
but it feels like
all we'll see is the tabletop.
[Not a magic carpet]
Honestly…
[Traveling in Egypt by dining table...]
I wonder if I even saw Egypt.
Right?
[Still]
The most important part of travel is food...!
- Right.
- That's right, that's right.
[A class act, for sure]
Let's quickly eat and go!
I'll eat one of those…
I'll also have one of these.
[Soon, the bottom of the plate starts showing]
I think it's the first time in my life
that I've eaten this much.
Then JISUNG, you take a break.
I'll finish all of this too!
[Eating it all on his own]
I need to take charge of this game!
[With the youngest
filling up his cheeks,]
[the older brothers
put on a final spurt too]
(One last piece)
- Yes, I will…
- Okay.
[Popped it in!]
[Team LEETEUK clears the grilled meat course!]
Did you already eat it?
But, you know,
we finished everything, right?
We just need to go!
After making one call!
(Trying to fish for their location)
No way...
LEETEUK...!
Yes?
Why are you
sending so many missions?
You promised not to do this…
[We did?]
Why, why, why?
Are you playing the game?
We're not able to eat the food!
That must be so fun!
Come on.
That's right!
(Phone call on hold)
We just need to flip one more.
- Just need to flip that one.
- Just flip that last one.
One?
[The worst phone etiquette]
What's the head and what's the tail?
So, this is one,
and this is one…
[But… Wait…]
That's right!
[They're not that far off]
Oh, we don't have time to watch this!
LEETEUK, hang up!
[If they flip the coin,
they’ll catch up in a flash]
No, like…
We're done!
Let's just go!
We're in big trouble.
Yeah. Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
[Meanwhile, this side’s also in big trouble]
Hey, we're in trouble, this is bad.
I think the pumping is important here!
Yeah, pump it up.
Pump it a lot!
Are there no cheap tricks
or anything like that for this?
But flipping 6 coins…
[A big amount: 600 won]
I never tried it, because I didn't have enough money.
[KIM YOHAN]
[Personal Best: 5 coins]
[Get into position]
That's it!
Hey, you got it!
- Oh! It's like this!
- It's this kind of vibe! Hey! Hey!
[The epitome of character growth]
Again, again, again!
I think it'll flip,
if I do it a bit more gently.
One person, keep doing it!
One person should keep doing it!
[YOHAN, let's go!]
Oof, I'm burping here.
[Cheering straight from the gut]
[YOHAN's relentless challenge continues]
[Change 6 heads]
[To tails]
- That's it!
- Oh!
[Two heads left]
Two! Two!
- Oh, okay!
- I'll flip it for you!
Be gentle with it! Be gentle.
[Let's continue with YOHAN's lucky streak!]
You just keep going. Just you alone.
I'll flip them quickly.
[Attempting right away!]
- Oh!
- That's it!
Ugh…Two! Two!!
It's two every time.
Again, again, again!
Just keep doing it!
Keep doing it! Just do it!
[Fourth attempt right away]
[Head → Tail]
[They all flipped…?]
[One head left]
One! One! One!
[Coin…You're driving us crazy…]
One, one! Again, again, again!
Wow,
but this is looking promising!
I feel like we'll get it!
[Changing it up to Tail → Head]
My hands are too small.
No, you can do it!
You've got this!
[Goal: 6 heads]
[Anxiously stomping his feet]
One! One! Wow…!
Wow, this is making me mad.
[So close]
One each time… Wow…
[To make things worse, the food's cooling down]
No, we're gonna get it soon.
[Team LEETEUK only has one more destination left]
There's only one place for dessert.
[About 50 minutes]
It's from one end to the other.
[The distance is the problem]
It's probably gonna take us an hour.
[After tying up the other team
with an attack item, they take off]
Oof!
Let’s go!
[CLEAR, CLEAR, Meat, Dessert]
[Team LEETEUK's To-Do: Move locations (50 minutes)]
Hurry up, please!
[Team SHINDONG's To-Do:
Flip Coins + Eat + Move locations (25 minutes)]
Oh no, no, no!
[The coin’s still being stubborn]
One! One, again! One! Wow!
No, we'll get it soon.
- We will, we will!
- It will happen!
It'll happen, YOHAN!
It will!
That was too weak...
Again, again.
[Everyone’s starting
to get anxious now]
...I have to do this, I have to.
[Carrying the burden
of the whole team]
[One careful, decisive move]
[Aiming for 6 heads this time too]
[1. Head]
[2. Head]
[3. Head]
[4. Head]
[5. Head]
[Please...]
[Just flip…]
[The last coin is...]
[Head]
[ALL CLEAR]
WE GOT IT!!
[We…]
[Got it]
Okay, we're good!
[Let’s go now!]
We're good! Eat, eat, eat! We're good!
Eat up, eat up!
Once again…
The ace always
shows up at times like this…
YOHAN…!
[KIM YOHAN / Personal best: 6 coins]
"Hmm? I think I should nudge it a bit."
"I don't think I should hit too hard."
As I was doing it,
I was able to get
the hang of it pretty quickly.
[Hehehehehe]
Why is the chunk
of meat in mine so big?
Hehe, this...
actually…
worked! Ohahaha!
[Still proud thinking about it]
Oh, the gelatin!
[Only three bowls of Kaware' left!]
Oh, I’m so full, what do I do?
YOHAN, you've got this!
We can't lose.
Hey, if we finish this,
I think we can win!
They went really far out.
They were still
at the restaurant, too.
[But Team LEETEUK is now on the move]
Today was not bad, not bad at all.
There was just too much lamb…
[Team LEETEUK is just as anxious]
The portion size was way bigger than expected.
[Let's eat quickly and catch up!]
Oh, we're properly
nourishing our bodies today.
[Amazed]
Guys, keep it up!
We’re almost there!
[Rising Food Fighter DAWN clears his bowl]
Wow!
[And Food Fighter YOHAN, as well]
YOHAN, almost there! Just hang in a bit more.
You're doing great.
I think it came
back up a little just now.
[Hnng…]
[Nourishing his body until the end]
[Team SHINDONG:
Meat course with boiled meat, CLEARED!]
Okay, can we head out now?
[Time to head to dessert]
Dessert? There’s only one spot for it, right?
Okay!
[Quickly checking the map]
Yeah, there’s just one place left.
[About 25 minutes]
We were here.
Here, here.
We have to head here now, right?
Okay.
Compared to coming from here,
[Around 50 minutes]
we're way faster.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Yeah, way faster, for sure.
Let's hurry!
We can win this!
[Around 25 minutes]
[Around 50 minutes]
[Team SHINDONG heads out late,
but is closer to the location]
[Meanwhile,
Team LEETEUK is already on the move]
[Can Team SHINDONG…]
We’re heading out!
[turn this situation around…?]
To the next location!
[Everyone heads to the final meetup place]
Ugh, I’m so full.
But honestly, today…
[Out of nowhere]
I had so much fun doing this with you guys.
Heh…!
[Why would you say that already?]
You kinda said it like we already lost.
[During the long ride]
But our vibe is completely different
[their confidence fades]
going there and coming back.
But did JOHNNY pick
everything today?
But…
[This romantic soul clings onto hope]
We honestly won.
Yeah, we won.
[What are you even saying?]
Won, exactly how?
Oh, so I mean…
It’s just that
the situation wasn’t on our side...
[Romantic human]
It’s all about romance, you know.
Romance?
[Romance copier]
It's romantic just being here.
But first,
I do think that
we're heading back defeated.
[Suddenly back to reality]
We shouldn’t have chased romance...
No.
We came
all the way to Egypt, after all.
JOHNNY, you seem like
you have a split personality right now.
So, our choices were solid
up to the second course.
[If only JOHNNYUS' luck]
Until the end,
[stayed with us…]
if we had picked boiled meat,
we would've
arrived 1-2 hours earlier.
Wow.
Right?
That's right.
But I'll say it again.
[Only romance]
I only made the romantic choices.
Nice.
[Staff]
Can you do an acrostic with "Romance"?
"Rom".
[Rom: Following romance]
"Following romance."
"Ance".
[Ance: …is all I did…]
"…is all I did…"
I really hope we win
after saying all that.
Seriously.
Then I'd be tearing up.
But honestly,
we are clinging to
that 1% chance of winning.
[Wishful thinking kicks in again]
We keep saying we lost, but hey, you never know.
- There's a thing called "You never know."
- It's like, "You never know."
[Lights OFF]
[Self-OUT]
[Darkness is needed for the leader's tears]
I felt like I was gonna cry…
I felt like I was gonna cry,
so I turned it off.
Okay.
[Following LEETEUK's example, OUT]
[Lights ON]
So, did we
become princes
or paupers?
[A broadcast-worthy performance]
Everyone, stay tuned for the reveal!
Nice.
They must be done eating
and on the way, right?
[CLEAR, CLEAR, CLEAR, Dessert]
Let's go for dessert!
It takes about 20 minutes, right?
Yeah, about that much.
I’m so curious...
Are they there?
At this rate,
aren’t we basically the princes?
But SHINDONG,
I've been thinking.
[Video call]
When LEETEUK called earlier,
what if they weren't
at the meat restaurant,
but the dessert place?
Huh? Already?
It could totally
be the dessert place
Because
(Fell asleep earlier)
we blacked out in the middle.
But if they were
at the dessert place…
If they finished eating the meat,
went to the dessert place,
and still gave us
an extra serving…
Ugh!
Then they're seriously the devil.
LEETEUK is a real devil.
Don't you get a feeling
they're hiding at the dessert place?
To get a shot of us
being really happy.
Ugh, that would be
the absolute worst.
If that happens,
it'd be so humiliating.
I think I can already
see LEETEUK's dimples.
With his dimples
dipping in as he smiles.
Because everyone is lying,
you just can't believe anything!
Even during the video calls,
[Staring hard at the background]
the background behind them…!
That's all we have
to figure things out.
Everything that was said then
was a complete lie.
[Four hours into the mission]
[Current time: 21:20]
[Cairo, a city of incredible scale]
Egypt is really huge.
The city is.
[YOHAN] It's a horse!
The horse is running.
Wow.
[Cars and horses share the road]
Wow, there’s a horse-drawn carriage.
[Sunset brings Cairo alive]
It’s crazy how lively it is at this hour.
This place looks
really amazing. Wow!
[Luxury buildings appear]
What is this place? Why is it so fancy? Wow!
The hotel is really tall.
I want to sleep
somewhere like that…
The hot water probably
just pours out there, right…?
It'd be amazing
to wake up in a place like that.
[We really, really want to be princes]
If you compare this to Korea, it'd be like a Han River view.
Oh, you’re right.
There was that hotel
with a pyramid view, too
That's right.
[Back to reality]
Even if we end up as paupers today,
let's not complain
and just sleep well.
[Losing it]
The mission was way too long.
Just coming to
Egypt was the mission.
I don't even think
Tom Cruise would do a mission this long.
And it’s still not over.
I think I'd be fine
with being a pauper today.
Because for today,
[Sleepy paupers]
all we have to do is sleep.
[Full paupers]
We finished eating all the food.
[Grateful paupers]
I'd just be thankful to sleep.
[Finding silver linings as a pauper while feeling anxious]
Hey, but pauper clothes might be more comfortable.
I like the pauper life.
I like v…vintage...
I'm saying this now,
but if we become princes, I'd be the happiest ever.
But can I tell you something?
We're feeling this way now,
[On the same wavelength]
and the other team is feeling the same way.
Right, right.
[They're seriously thinking the same thing]
Still, you never know. Let's not lose hope.
I would be over the moon.
- If we win, seriously…
- Yeah, I'd be so happy.
[Overjoyed at the thought of being a prince]
I might even seriously cry.
If I really become
a prince today,
when you guys
make your comeback,
I’m sending you a coffee truck.
[A prince's promise]
[A heartfelt coffee truck gift]
Because I’m so thankful to you guys.
[Team Prince, let's go!]
Like, "Team Prince! Let's go!"
[Who sent it is important]
"Sent by Prince SHINDONG"
Hahahahaha!
[Team SHINDONG,
who's getting closer]
[Team LEETEUK,
who finished eating and headed out first]
[A full-course dining race
shaped by their decisions]
They say baseball starts
at the bottom of the 9th with two outs.
The 9th inning magic.
Why am I suddenly
getting butterflies...!
I seriously hope
they're not there.
[Who will win the final course]
Please, please.
[to take it all?]
JISUNG’s hoping hard.
[Only the princes will enjoy]
[An epic view of the pyramids]
[A 5-star hotel]
[Meanwhile,
today's accommodation for the paupers]
[Bivouacking in a tent
out in the middle of nowhere]
[Who will be destined to bivouac?]
[The final meetup spot for
"The Pharaoh's Table" by the Nile River]
[Which team arrived first?]
- We're here!
- We're almost there! Almost there!
Oh, but…
There are way too many cars.
What’s going on?
- Oh, there are so many cars.
- So many.
The cars we're using
all look the same.
And so many of them were there.
[Cars per team]
We usually have around 2-3 cars.
[Numbers 1 through 9 are all there]
Buses 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9
were all there.
Seeing that, I thought,
"Oh…It's over…"
"They're all here."
Oh, Team LEETEUK is here…
It’s okay!
We still did really well.
[Trudging along]
[Team SHINDONG arrives at the dessert shop]
Oh, what’s this?
- Wow!
- Wow! What's this?
- Oh!
- Huh?
What?
This isn't where LEETEUK was earlier!
[The place looks different from the video call background]
This isn’t the same spot
- I think we came here first.
- We won!
- Oh?
[Empty]
We won…
[Confused]
For real?
[Excitement rises with the empty room]
Did we win?
Oh, I think we really won.
Wait, they're not here at all!
[Tiptoeing in]
No one's here.
- They're not here!
- Really? For real?
For real?
[A mystery: Is Team LEETEUK hiding?]
Hurry and come out! Where are you?
[Please tell us]
Wait, did we actually win?
Come on,
just tell us honestly now.
[Calming down and sitting]
Let's sit down first. Let's sit.
Seriously?
[Eyes darting around anxiously]
The people who picked grilled meat
seem to be stuck
in traffic right now.
For real?!
- This is insane! Seriously!
- Hey, hey, this is crazy!
[Then we're the princes today?!]
Then are all three of us princes?
[Pure joy]
Seriously?
[Staff] Now, everyone,
the victory to become princes
is right before your eyes.
Why "right before our eyes"…?
We basically got it.
There's still
one more hurdle to pass.
Ugh, why do you
keep giving us hurdles?
Everyone, there are
six water bottles in front of you.
[Suspiciously been there since earlier]
Oh, I think this is gonna be brutal.
[Staff] Without
knocking over a single bottle,
[Final challenge: Remove the tablecloth]
you must pull out the tablecloth underneath.
[Jumping up]
SHINDONG, I'm really good at this.
You know
the show "Dad's Challenge"?
[Turns out it’s his specialty]
I'm really good at this.
I’ve done this before…
[Succeeded on the first try]
I nailed it right away for our original content.
[Source: OUI ENTERTAINMENT]
For real?
YOHAN's gonna be good at this!
[Smiles blossom at the experienced pro's arrival]
Is it this way, or this way? Which way?
- I need to pull it out smoothly this way.
- This side?
Okay!
Let’s go!
[Team SHINDONG has a wildcard]
YOHAN is the wildcard in our team.
YOHAN's good at things like this.
You can do it!
[Staff] Let me
break down the rules for you.
Among the three of you,
[If even one succeeds]
If even one person makes it,
[Tea & dessert served]
you'll get to enjoy tea and desserts right away.
Okay.
If all three fail,
[If all fail: Locked out for 3 minutes]
you'll be locked out for 3 minutes.
Oh, okay, okay.
[Before Team LEETEUK arrives]
Let’s hurry, SHINDONG. It's better to do it quickly!
[they need to speed up]
Should we do it first?
[Dependable]
Should we just finish it in one go?
Let's just finish it in one go!
[Whoosh]
Finish it in one go. Finish it.
YOHAN will take
the final challenge.
Yes, I’ll go first.
YOHAN! YOHAN!
- I think YOHAN will do it.
- Oh, but the bottles aren't entirely full.
Here I go!
Let's go, YOHAN! Let's go!
Let's go!
[Team SHINDONG's muscle man]
[He won the team's only attack item by muscle alone]
Nice.
Good job, good job.
[Even when they were under attack by Team LEETEUK]
It'll work. This will work.
[He was Team SHINDONG's reliable problem solver]
Okay okay! We got it!
[Taking the challenge with all his power]
Here I go.
Let's go, YOHAN!
Let's go!
Ack!
[A polite bow]
Ack! What's this?
[He's a bit of a bluffer]
Hey, what are you doing?
[Confidence vs. reality]
Hey, you said you were good at this.
This is hard…
They all just fell down.
[Raising an issue]
But this material is not really great...
[Analyzing the cause of failure]
It should be silk or something like that.
Come on, this is…!
Should we use the back side?
We can use the back side, right?
Oh, it's okay.
Oh! Hey, the back side…
[Quickly switching the material]
Yeah, let's use the back.
[Strategy: Use the smooth side for less friction]
We got it, we got it.
This is better,
this is way better.
When they come,
don't tell them
any tips on how to do it.
And bring the bottles closer together.
[Adjusting water bottle spacing]
Closer, closer.
So they support each other.
I’m gonna give it a shot first.
You're gonna do it, SHINDONG?
I'm doing it!
Ack!
(Do it)
[SHINDONG steps up for the final challenge]
Challenge accepted!
ACK!
[4 bottles remain standing]
[Excited]
Hey, I got a feeling! I got a feeling!
[Survival rate skyrockets]
You too, right? We got it, we got it.
Let's just hurry
and do it! Quick!
(Are they coming?)
We have to do it quickly.
We have to do it
before they come.
First, pull it a bit.
[DAWN steps up for the final challenge]
Challenge accepted!
[Flap]
[Fail]
It's fine, it's fine. 3 minutes!
[The 3-minute lockout timer starts]
Alright, alright, timer, timer.
Ack!
- This is so hard.
- Start it, start it.
[Practicing during their 3-minute lockout]
We can practice during this time, right?
- You can practice.
- Practicing doesn't matter.
[Lights ON]
We
We lost...
[Lights OFF]
But I’m curious.
Are you okay with losing, LEETEUK?
We lost because of you.
I'm fine with losing,
because we gave it our all.
- Yeah…
- That's right, we did our best.
I don’t think
you’re really okay with it?
I was wondering,
"Did we give it our best?"
Oh, you didn't give it your best?
Not me, but you…
[Flustered by
his teammate’s complaint]
Why me?
I really did my best.
[Joking]
Honestly, LEETEUK, you were pretty solid.
We all worked hard.
We all worked very hard.
[6 lamb chops]
You had six lamb chops.
Only you could pull that off.
6 lamb chops are really…!
I actually got gentle after that.
Because I ate too much lamb.
Baaaaaaa!
Wow.
[Lights OFF]
Good night.
This is fun.
[Lights ON]
If it's gonna be like this,
let's just keep
going with this team!
How about we keep
going with this team?
[Anticipation]
We click well, right? What do you think?
We do click well.
But I'm curious how
SHINDONG does things.
[Lights OFF]
[Lights ON]
JISUNG probably thinks differently, right?
[Anticipation, Round 2]
What about you, JISUNG?
[Lights ON]
I will…
not comment.
[Lights OFF]
But LEETEUK, I didn't know
you were this kind of character.
[Low-key always a target]
LEETEUK, you're really an all-rounder.
I am.
This is fun.
Sigh…
[Honest]
I hope the winner’s hotel is super far away…
[Sincere blessings]
[Meanwhile, Strategist SHINDONG’s game plan time]
Hey, let’s figure out what works best.
Hey, try putting them
all to one side
The two tables are split here.
[Strategist SHINDONG thinks it through]
I set up a plan. So, what is it?
Is it better to line up
the bottles in a row?
Or is it better
to set it up like this?
[Testing to get a feel for it]
So we tried it out
in a variety of ways.
Does it matter
how we place the bottles?
Nope!
Then let’s do it like this.
[Adjusting the water bottles’ arrangement]
Like this.
How much time left?
One minute passed.
[YOHAN gives it a practice run]
Ugh!
Try it one more time.
[Having one person get the hang of it for now]
One person needs to quickly get the hang of it.
Do I need to pull it really hard?
[Pocket billiards formation]
Like, pool balls.
In the middle, in the middle.
[Fail]
Ugh…
No, no, this isn’t it.
This is so hard, so hard.
Hey, you've got this.
You can do it.
Again, again!
[Still didn't get the hang of it]
I think it's best if you do it, SHINDONG…
When you did it,
it was the most…
How about this?
[Wobble]
Ugh!
[So close yet so far]
This is possible to do, right?
[Trying to set it on the edge this time]
I think we have to keep it towards the edge.
[Swoosh]
You got the vibe, right?
[Thud-thud]
[After various attempts]
You sorta got it, right?
[They inch closer to success]
Is it time? 3 minutes are up? Hurry and look.
[The 3-minute lockout time ends]
We got it, we got it.
We got it.
Hey, do it.
[Trying again before losing the groove]
Hey, YOHAN, go! YOHAN go!
- Just go, just go!
Challenge accepted!
[YOHAN’s second attempt]
[Thud-Thunk]
Agh…!
This is driving me crazy! ACK!!!
I'll do it before you, SHINDONG.
[DAWN’s second attempt]
Challenge accepted! DAWN!
Challenge accepted!
Let’s do this!
[Casting a hopeful spell]
You could be the one to nail it.
That’s right, you got this!
Well, I mean, you think
[Self-doubt]
I would nail this?
[Swish]
[Ding]
Agh!
[Currently the best record]
[Success: 5 bottles, Fail: 1 bottle]
[Almost there now]
Ugh, seriously.
- Just do it, just do it!
- We're almost there, SHINDONG.
Wow, you had 5 standing…!
[Next up, SHINDONG]
I got it, I got it. I get it now.
[Team LEETEUK arrives!]
SHINDONG, you have to do it!
Is it here?
[SHINDONG’s second try]
Challenge accepted!
They're here! They're here!
They're here!
- Wait, wait!
- Where? Where?
[Team LEETEUK]
But we should at least explain it to them.
[Curious]
What kind of game is this?
Alright, welcome!
Come this way!
This way, please!
Everyone, I’ve got good news.
Come quickly.
[What's there to be happy about?]
What good news do you have?
The game isn’t over yet.
Why? Why? Why?
[To Team LEETEUK]
The team that completes this mission first
[The final mission is announced]
wins the whole thing
We’ve been failing non-stop.
You know when you pull this out?
So we came here first
and have been trying it, but…
[Dessert]
Aren’t we supposed to eat?
No, no.
[The final challenge for the dessert]
We have to do this to get dessert.
[Processing the situation]
SHINDONG, how long have you been here?
[Lying without hesitation]
We've been here for like 30 minutes.
We got locked out
3 times already.
I'm getting hopeful!
[It's not the time to give up]
LEETEUK, it's not the end!
It's not over,
it's not over at all.
[Staff] Now that you’re here,
[No more 3-minute lockouts]
the 3-minute lockout has been removed,
- Oh, it's not a thing anymore?
- Yeah.
Oh, since they're here! Okay.
[The teams will take turns]
Each team will take turns
and try it one at a time.
Take turns? Okay.
After the team that succeeds
[After enjoying the provided tea & dessert]
enjoys the provided tea and dessert
[Shout "I am the prince!" to win]
you just have to shout "I am the prince!"
Oh, okay, okay.
Wait…They're really
giving me hope until the end!
The staff keeps giving me hope!
That fabric is different from ours.
It's the same.
- Oh, you can do it like this.
- It's the same. It's the same.
[Sharing info like a generous gift]
You can flip it, too. It's the same thing.
[Got it!]
We just have to figure it out.
Should we do this seriously?
[Staff] Since SHINDONG was
about to go, you can do it first.
They've done it a lot,
so they must have some tricks up their sleeves.
[Setting up carefully]
Isn't it better to put one on that side?
- Should we put it on this side?
- Yes.
How many bottles
have you done so far?
[Team SHINDONG's best record: DAWN 5 bottles]
We just did 5 bottles.
- Really? DAWN did?
- Yeah, he got 5 standing, but failed.
[SHINDONG’s second attempt]
Challenge accepted!
[Habitual lying]
This is our 3rd lockout!
[Shaking]
[Success]
Wow!!!
[Succeeded
before Team LEETEUK could even try]
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
[Electrifying]
You guys planned that, right?
[Impeccable timing, like they staged it]
No, we didn't! We didn't plan it.
I was honestly
so disappointed in SHINDONG.
No, like this guy…!
If this is the first time
the prince and pauper are being chosen on this trip,
we should all
try it a few times each!
But he nailed it in one try
and killed the vibe.
This guy's been
on air since forever.
I expected
more from him than that.
LEETEUK doesn't really
understand how editing works.
If you watch the full show later,
it'll be really entertaining.
You'll be clutching your stomach,
laughing nonstop,
to the point
you'll surprise yourself.
While I was practicing,
I thought, "For this…"
"Speed is everything!"
And…
It's not an arm snap!
It's a wrist snap!
Swish!
I went for it, and it worked!
Success!!!!
When SHINDONG
just pulled it out quickly…
The bottles went back and forth.
I thought
I was on the Viking ride.
They went back and forth,
and when they finally stopped,
I also returned to the middle.
That moment
was seriously electrifying.
[Gives him the chills thinking about it]
SHINDONG, my heart literally skipped a beat.
I was really surprised too.
[Strategist SHINDONG completes the final challenge]
They were like wobbling!
We just need to do this quickly!
Yeah, do it!
We can just do it quickly!
JISUNG, this one's on you.
Wow, how do I even do this?
Come on,
that one's impossible.
One, two, three!
[Swoosh]
Oh, okay.
I got the vibe.
- It's not easy.
- It's hard, it's hard.
[Successful Team SHINDONG gets their tea & desserts]
Spread this on there.
[The Full-Course Dining Mission: "The Pharaoh’s Table"]
[The Final Course]
[Staff] Team LEETEUK,
you can keep trying it.
But we have to
eat this quickly instead!
[Black tea & chocolate dates]
But hey, this is hot!
(Very hot)
How can you give us something hot in this weather?
JOHNNY's doing it!
[JOHNNY’s first attempt]
Let’s go!
[JOHNNY’s first fail]
[Busy / Chill]
But we have to enjoy it with ease.
[Starting with
a bite of the chocolate date]
I'm gonna watch them with ease!
Let's watch them!
[LEETEUK’s first try]
Challenge accepted!
Agh!!
Hey, eat faster.
Eat faster!
Ow, hot!
Hey, I think I can nail this.
[Way too hot to rush]
I think I can nail this.
[JISUNG’s second try]
Challenge accepted! One, two, three!
[JISUNG’s second fail]
Whew.
Ow, hot!
Hey, eat slowly!
You'll burn your tongue!
This is seriously hot.
[Sip]
Ack... hnng…
[The fail count keeps climbing]
I can relax a bit now.
I think I’m getting
the hang of this.
After two tries, I kinda get it.
- Is it this?
- Yeah.
[Starting to find their rhythm]
It's this, but in an instant…!
Team Pauper, you can do this!
[Received cheering that shattered their focus]
Wow, that's really triggering.
Let’s go, JISUNG!
[JISUNG’s third attempt]
Challenge accepted!
JISUNG’s pauper challenge!
Haha...
Two
[Fail]
Aw, man!
[Meanwhile,
SHINDONG clears the tea & the dessert]
[Fail]
Agh!
So close.
[Wobble]
[Plop]
Wow.
Was that the wind…?
Okay…
[YOHAN clears his dessert]
Is something wrong on that side?
[A game full of romance]
Let’s just have fun and call it a day
You should still nail it once!
I have to show that I'm the big bro
at times like this! You saw it earlier, right?
You did it the best!
[The big bro who aims to be a solid leader]
Putting it near the edge!
[And the little bros
who watch with trust…]
Challenge accepted!
[Success]
Oh!
[This team's eldest seals the deal, too]
That's what I'm talking about.
Nice.
[Casually refilling the water]
Even refilling it.
Plenty of time for a refill.
I'll start over from the top, LEETEUK.
[Team LEETEUK gets their tea & dessert too]
Oh…
If you finish that quickly,
you could win!
[Chill]
Our concept is romance!
Because JOHNNY said
we're Team Romance.
Don’t lose our pace now.
[Keep it romantic till the end]
Keep it cool till the very last moment.
DAWN, let’s finish this.
Let's hurry and be princes.
I’m the pauper...
[Gulp]
I'm the prince.
One, two, three!
I’m the prince!
Nice…
[SHINDONG, DAWN, YOHAN
confirmed as the 1st princes]
Wow!
That was one long journey.
We had no idea we'd win.
I’m the prince!
But I really thought
we would lose.
We didn't pick a leader,
but I was
basically like the leader.
If they took my lead
and became paupers to sleep outside,
I think they would've blamed me.
Lucky for us,
we became princes!
Can I even say this?
I'm over the moon…?
Yeah, I think
that's the right word.
We were like,
hugging each other like crazy.
I was like, "What even is this..?"
[What even is this that it brought us together?]
I think we bonded hard then.
[Moving to their respective accommodations
based on their prince or pauper status]
We did it.
[The princes happily board the car]
We became princes.
[Caught the staff
chatting with the driver]
[Team Prince gains hotel intel]
(YOHAN instantly looks it up)
This is awesome.
- How did we actually win?
- Right?
Wow…
I pulled it,
[Looking back, the last mission was a nail-biter]
and it started shaking like crazy at first! Wow.
- Wow, seriously.
- You saw it earlier, right?
You thought they'd fall, right?
They would've fallen
if they had a little less water.
[Finished searching up the hotel]
One of Cairo’s
5-star hotels that's quite famous.
- Oh!
- Wow, it's gonna be amazing.
[A royal family villa that became a hotel!]
It was later renovated as a hotel.
[Prince's accommodation, Day 1]
There’s a lobby outside that feels like a real palace.
[Situated in front
of the Giza Plateau]
[A 5-star hotel
with a view of the pyramids!]
[And the princes' room there]
Let's go and see what the princes' rooms are like!
[On the way to see it now]
Wow, I think
it's gonna be incredible.
[A grand hallway welcomes the princes]
It’s got serious vibes.
Wow, this is…
There’s definitely
a different vibe here.
- The hotel hallway is huge.
- Exactly, compared to everything so far.
[Totally blown away from the hallway]
The hallway is so huge.
Wow, this hallway
is seriously so wide.
You know, the fancier the hotel,
the fewer floors it actually has?
It’s long.
That’s why
the hallway’s super wide.
I’ve never seen
such a wide hotel hallway before!
[The majestic hallway
raises expectations even more]
[Full of heart flutters]
Wow, I’m getting excited.
Hey, it's here.
[The princes each find their rooms]
My room's here.
This is my room.
Go find your rooms now.
Yes.
[The song that unites all generations kicks in]
Ppara-ppara-ppam!
- Ppara-ppara!
[In awe from the first step in]
Wow!
[Befitting a royal villa]
Just amazing…!
Wow!
[An accommodation
with a classic vibe]
[A pyramid-view terrace included!]
[It's the breakfast spot
with an absolutely gorgeous view]
Oh!
[Officially checking out the room]
Yes, the hotel's the way to go!
Alright, let’s see
what we've got here.
What is this?
Wow…!
[The moment he spots the terrace]
Oh!
[Cheers explode]
[The prince is loving this terrace]
Wow, this terrace is the best.
[A special performance
just for the prince’s arrival!]
[So exciting]
Wow.
First…
Let me just lie here for a second.
Ugh…
[Dives straight onto the bed]
AGH!
This is so nice.
[This is what being a prince is all about]
I could just fall asleep right now.
Oh, what's this?
[Meanwhile, DAWN and YOHAN…]
This place is so pleasant.
[Terrace spotted]
A terrace!
- Wow!
- There's a terrace! Wow!
There's a performance
going on over there right now!
It's this kind of vibe!
They're performing over there!
[Enjoying the terrace concert
in the middle of the night]
[All the princes fall for the terrace view]
The view was nice, and it was completely wide open.
"So, this is what
success really tastes like…"
That’s what I realized.
Coincidentally, there happened
to be a wedding going on over there!
[Prince SHINDONG loved it all, including the performance]
So, the lights were moving all over the place.
EDM was playing.
Wow!
I realized it today.
I am
[With a vow to be a prince again tomorrow]
determined to be a prince again tomorrow
[Time to hit the hay]
I wonder
what the paupers are up to.
Paupers, show yourselves!
[Team Pauper appears in low spirits]
[Gloomy]
[Mixed feelings]
[Even at Team Pauper's accommodation]
As you all loved earlier, the pauper accommodation
[There is romance…?]
is a place full of romance.
It's full of romance?
Full of romance.
So, in a way
[Add romance]
In a way, it could be romantic, right?
[To romance]
Let’s just choose romance.
[And to more romance]
We agreed to go for romance.
[JOHNNY was on Team Romance all day]
We chased after romance!
We're chasing after romance.
Nice, nice.
I think…
[No more romance]
we don't need to be romantic now.
We chased after romance,
[Giving up on romance after becoming a pauper]
and found hardship.
[According to JOHNNY, the ultimate romantic...]
My basic aesthetic is chasing after romance!
If a trip is too easy,
it won't be memorable.
[So I’m choosing the hard life]
It's like, I'm searching for hardship.
(Why did I do that...)
[JISUNG, let's toss romance aside]
[Already given up]
Let's just go and sleep.
[A dark path ahead, just like how they feel...]
The road ahead is pitch black.
It’s so dark,
just like my feelings
[A brutal off-road trail appears]
The boulders up ahead are insane!
I hate this so much.
I really hate this.
Oh…!
[A special service for Team Pauper]
I'm sorry, but I'm not gonna be a pauper!
[Off-road romance]
Please just send me home already.
That was legendary just now.
Wow, that was seriously legendary.
[Finally, Team Pauper arrives somewhere]
How far are we going in?
[First getting out into the darkness]
Wow…
Wow…!
I can see the stars!
[They said no more romance,
but the younger paupers keep searching for it]
You can see them.
I can see one.
It must be a satellite.
If we turn off the lights,
we could probably see them better.
[Cairo is a famous spot for stars]
[Forget adventure, the older pauper is just tired]
It’s 1:20 a.m. right now.
We’ve been awake
for almost 40 hours straight,
and we have to
be up again in 4 hours.
But can the camera
even capture this right now?
Just how far…
Can people see where we are?
[This pitch-dark place is actually]
[A chill camping spot with all the vibes]
[Wadi Degla Protectorate]
[This was filmed safely with
prior permission from the authorities]
[The first pauper accommodation]
The first "ALL or NOTHING" pauper accommodation is this way.
Hold up.
[The pauper vibe is stronger than imagined]
Oh, please, no…
- This is the real pauper life
- Oh, wait.
Wow, this is legit pauper status.
Wow, I'm really a pauper…
This is all real.
[Who am I? Where am I?]
Wow. Why am I here, plus…
I realized that
[Baby JISUNG thrown]
I've been really spoiled,
[into this brutal variety show world]
and I've been a pretty happy guy
all this time.
Honestly, I was kinda stunned.
I didn’t expect it
to be this intense.
[Left stranded in a barren desert...]
I had no clue they’d just dump us here.
That wasn't an accommodation!
[Pure shock]
I was so shook. For real.
Shouldn’t there be
at least a ceiling or something?
Oh, LEETEUK.
[JOHNNY looks excited, considering he was left behind]
If you ask me, this is that.
We set it?
This is a tent.
It's a tent?
- LEETEUK.
- Yeah.
[Big smile]
Seriously, just once, just once!
Stop spewing nonsense.
Just open it once.
- Open what?
- Your heart.
[JOHNNY / LEETEUK]
[Romantic Team Pauper's spear and shield]
It is pretty cool.
What's cool?
[The unbreakable romantic shield]
It's so dark, you can't even see anything.
Isn't it cool because it's dark?
[The pauper leader assesses the situation]
What's this?
[Checking supplies]
They only gave us three bottles of water.
Three measly bottles of water?!
It’s a humidifying mask.
[The survival kit includes humidifying masks and bread]
A humidifying mask…
From what I can tell,
[Today's home: Tent found]
it's a tent.
Open it up.
Yeah, that must be it.
Go ahead and open it.
LEETEUK, have you ever
set up a tent before?
[Can only trust LEETEUK, who's served in the army]
It’s been ages since I set up a tent.
First, you have to untie this.
[Even though he has mixed feelings…]
Hah…
[When his younger bros seek him out]
Wait, wait, what's this?
Isn't this
[He transforms into a grumbling problem-solver]
one of those pop-up tents?
Don't you just spread it open?
Wow, that's a relief!
[LEETEUK naturally takes charge]
Wow.
That’s a relief.
[Immediately figured out the tent]
Oh, this is that. It just sets up.
Wow, thank goodness, for real.
[The grumbling pauper suddenly takes the lead]
Hey, hey, this one, over here on the side.
Oh, what?
This is super convenient!
Isn't this only for one person?
[Complaints bubble up again]
This isn't the Han River or anything!
[But his younger bros seem super hyped]
Hey, but it’s pretty spacious!
No, like, more than expected.
Do you guys…
find this fun?
[Yeah, it’s fun]
It is kind of fun.
It's fun? Sigh…!
I was seriously so mad,
but they kept saying,
"LEETEUK, this is so great!"
JOHNNY's like,
"LEETEUK, this is so romantic."
[The oldest pauper
gets more and more conflicted]
- It is kind of fun.
- Yeah, it's fun.
It's fun? Sigh…!
But wait a sec,
we're right on top of a boulder.
Let’s find somewhere flat!
[LEETEUK trait]
[Complains, but works the hardest]
Right here.
[Thanks to the grumbling pauper's efforts,
the pauper accommodation is finally complete]
JISUNG, do you like it?
[Next quest]
I have a feeling that
[Laying out the mat inside the tent]
we can't spread this out completely.
[For some reason]
We gotta fold it up about this much
[The grumbling pauper is holding it]
to use it.
LEETEUK, please do it.
Move aside.
[So fed up]
Ugh!!!
[ROMANTIC BABOZ]
Hey, you were so eager to do this earlier,
[who don't know how to do anything]
but now that we're doing it…
[LEETEUK eventually steps in]
But because you are good at this…
No, it's not
that I'm good at this.
[The grumbling pauper still works hard]
We can't do anything about this.
- It just needs to overlap.
- Yeah, let's spread it out,
and just…
[Leads by example + Gives clear orders = Great leader]
Remember those big rocks from before?
Put them on the inside, like this.
Hand me a rock.
[Mentally checked out]
Ugh!!
I just wanna go home!!
[But he's physically working hard]
Hand me a rock.
Ugh!!!
[He's definitely a good leader]
Oh, but LEETEUK really did it well for us.
[I invite you to my pauper tent]
Come in.
But aren't deserts
supposed to get cold at night?
[Zen mode activated]
You'll get cold as you sleep.
JISUNG, come inside.
I really don't think
this place is right…What do you think?
- It's alright, though.
- It's not so bad.
It's not bad.
It's bad!!!
If we had a fire and some ramyeon,
it'd be perfect.
[What do you mean? We have neither]
We don't have a fire or ramyeon.
- That's why I'm bummed.
- No, so like…
Don't think about the "What ifs"!
[The pauper leader is sharp at reading the situation]
Take a moment and look at the situation we're in!
If this place isn't so bad,
then are you
gonna keep being paupers?
Think about Team Prince!
Right now, they're comfortably
[The leader tries]
sleeping on king-sized beds.
[to motivate the team members]
They have their own rooms and can have hot showers.
They probably started sleeping, like 1-2 hours ago.
- Here are your final supplies.
- Oh? What's this?
[Bedding is provided for the paupers]
This is a sleeping bag.
[Romantic JOHNNY is happy even with a sleeping bag]
Oh!
How do we use this?
It gets hot in here.
[The grumpy pauper
wants a room of his own]
Ugh…
[Successfully moved out]
JOHNNY.
But LEETEUK.
Yeah?
[JOHNNY is still a positive romantic]
Your body is gonna feel so refreshed.
[This isn't just a foot reflexology]
It's like those acupressure slippers,
[It’s a full-body reflexology!]
but actually, acupressure for the body!
Acupressure for the body.
This is not the time to be laughing.
[With his back to his team members]
We have to win no matter what tomorrow
[the leader lays down his vision]
and become princes!
You know?
But I don't think
we'll be on the same team.
[Suddenly JOHNNY goes into savage mode]
JOHNNY, were you always this cold?
Yes.
[LEETEUK gets
abandoned by the Romantics]
Ugh! I'm so annoyed!
I need to ditch these guys.
I need to survive on my own.
I shouldn't do team battles.
JISUNG and JOHNNY…
[Team Pauper is falling apart?!?]
I have to ditch them.
That thought crossed my mind.
You're so cold.
I’m feeling so lonely right now.
Come inside, LEETEUK.
I should just
use this as a pillow.
[Before LEETEUK's return]
Oh, this isn’t so bad.
[The pauper siblings tidy things up]
I’ll just use it as a pillow.
[The grumpy pauper
eventually heads back inside]
[Always keeps his bedding neat]
[ROMANTIC BABOZ
are still quite satisfied]
Wow, LEETEUK.
But LEETEUK,
this is really nice!
[I don't like it!!!!]
Ugh!!!
[Time for the paupers to sleep]
Paupers, get some good sleep tonight.
Are you really
leaving us like this?
We're sleeping
right next to you, too.
But you calling
a pauper "a pauper"…
As a pauper,
it's really offensive!
- Now that I think about it, yeah…
- It makes you angry, right?
- That is really annoying.
- Hey, JOHNNY. You have to remember that!
[Only mad now after someone called him a pauper]
We need to leave this pauper life behind.
[The paupers are so different from the princes]
Honestly, I’ve just given up.
I'll see you in the morning.
[Trying to turn off the tent light...]
How do I turn this off?
UGH!
[The paupers can't even turn off the light]
There's nothing Team Pauper can do…
Can't even turn off the light.
[While fiddling with the light]
[A club opens]
- This is a club.
- Wow, it's a club!
Whoo!
[A special desert club
created just for the romantic Team Pauper]
So it has this feature too.
- Is it okay?
- No.
[It's really bedtime now]
Oh, there we go.
Ugh.
Let's be princes tomorrow.
[Falling asleep,
determined to be a prince tomorrow]
I'm gonna do it.
Me too.
That feeling starts to set in.
"I'm really not
gonna be a pauper."
I promised myself
that I would definitely be a prince.
No matter what happens tomorrow,
I’m gonna be a prince
[And so, everyone]
I became so determined that I thought,
[dreams of moving up]
"Whether I look good or bad on camera,"
"I'm gonna be a prince."
Goodnight, everyone.
[Will they really
become princes tomorrow…?]
Good night.
Sleep well.
[Everything changes for next week]
[Egypt Trip, Day 2]
Let's go to the next stop.
["ALL or NOTHING" heads to a new city]
Let’s go!
[LUXOR]
Luxor.
This is so cool.
How is this
still standing after all this time?
[The world’s largest outdoor museum]
Whoa, this is pretty cool.
[Where the dead and living meet]
The prime resting place of kings.
Wow, look at this!
[Waiting for them there is...]
Oh, there’s a pool!
[The highlight of the Luxor trip]
Wow, Luxor!
The game's over.
This is serious luxury.
[Luxury cruise]
Wow, this is insane.
[Excitement level 100%]
Wow!
- This is nuts!
- So crazy!
[If you’re a pauper, you can't get on board]
Isn’t this too good to be true?
Wow, this place is amazing.
Let’s just travel
without battling.
Let's just all sleep together
without doing any missions!
[Nope, go back]
[To board]
The luggage is here! The luggage is here!
[You gotta take your luggage]
Wait, what is this?
[If you fail to save your luggage]
I haven't properly
unpacked my bags yet.
[Chosen as Today's Pauper]
Super poor!
Ugh, I hate this so much!
[To save your luggage]
This is going too far!
Way too far!
LEETEUK!
[Fight with everything you’ve got]
How are you supposed to run fast like this?
[Activate your brainpower!]
Wait, I know this one! Ugh!
Hold on, my memory is…!
[Their endlessly]
Ack!!
[Changing]
Woo-hoo!
[Fate]
Oh, this one…
Ack!
Wow!
Whoo!
[So, who’ll make it
onto the cruise as princes...?]